[Music]
all right so today I'm going to be doing
an unboxing and review for the Desai
Mochi 3 the little driving companion
robot that so many people have been
talking about you probably saw this on
social media for a while what you see me
unboxing here to the left is the actual
Mochi the actual robot and everything
that you can expect for it to come with
again this is the version three which is
the latest version not to be confused
with the second one so as you can see
the first thing you will notice when you
open it is the instruction manual know
it does not come with any stickers or
anything like that this is just a little
manual showing you how it works the
animation and all that how to remove the
helmet which is something that a lot of
people have a hard time figuring out
this is how the little robot actually
arrives it already has the little helmet
attached and as you can see mine is
black there are multiple colors this is
the midnight black you have to see what
color is available not all of them are
available the first challenge you will
likely have is how to turn it on and how
to remove the helmet it is not intuitive
at all the second thing you will notice
are these velcro uh things that you use
to attach on the car and the charging
cable observe how I go ahead head and
remove the helmet this is how most
people do it you can technically just
use your nails but that's how you do it
and then to the side of the Mochi you
will see the on switch it's very small
and easy to miss but that's how you turn
it on as you can see it already greets
you and it starts doing some random
animations now I'm going to be unboxing
DRX Gundam battle helmet which
unfortunately is not something you can
really buy at the Dy store anymore it's
been out of stock for a long time I
don't think it's ever going to come back
to stock from my understanding I had a
buy this off of somebody because I
really really wanted it and it's pretty
hard to find so if you can get your
hands on one of those I would say
cherish it so this is how you remove and
attach new helmets to the Mochi 3 you
will know it's secure and in place once
you hear a snap like a little click you
will know that it is secure fair to
mention that this helmet was actually
designed for the version two of the
doochi but it is compatible with the
third version I really wanted a third
version that's why I didn't get the
second one and the main reason for that
is because the second version the number
two requires a cable at all times the
dasai Mochi 3 what's actually pretty
cool about it is that you can recharge
it and it does not need to be connected
to the cable at all times to be working
that's a cool feature that they've
introduced because what that means is
that the Mochi turns off by itself the
version 3 Mochi does not need to be
turned off manually you can but you
don't have to if it detects no movement
or nothing happening in your car after a
minute it will just turn off which is
nice because if every single time you
have to remove the helmet and manually
turn it off that would be annoying which
is the case with the second second
version of it the Mochi 2 requires not
only to be connected to a wire at all
times it's always on unless you turn it
off the Mochi 3 is nice because every
time you get into your car and you start
your car it's almost like it's greeting
you and if you're not using it or you're
parked it'll just turn off that's a good
thing because not only does it conserve
battery but it also extends the life of
the little robot because if you haven't
been able to tell the quality is not the
best it's very cute and very nice
looking but if I'm being honest it's not
the best quality at all and honestly for
the price that they're charging it'll
fall somewhere between like 50 to 60
bucks you get like a firsttime buyer
discount so it'll fall somewhere in that
range for that price tag I would be
expecting a lot more quality now to be
fair it is just a random little company
that came out of nowhere and kind of
blew up on social media they have been
slowly but surely improving their
product and I would expect that 5 or 10
years from now if it's still a thing it
would be a little bit better quality so
these are really the early stages but
with that said as somebody that owns
other robots and other gadgets like I've
owned a vector for a long time the
quality is just not the same I to be
honest with you I probably wouldn't
expect this thing to last maybe more
than 2 to 3 years I would expect the
third version this version to have a
little bit more durability because again
it's not constantly on it turns off on
its own and it doesn't have to
constantly be plugged in which increases
the longevity and the life so this right
here is where most people seem to choose
to put their Mochi just behind the
steering wheel I personally don't leave
it there I actually leave it on top of
the navigation system which I'm going to
show you later on the video there's a
couple reasons for that reason number
one I don't like leaving it there is
because I found it very distracting you
know how my car is designed you can see
it's kind of covering the speed limit it
covers a few different things and I'm
constantly looking at it if it's there
it's not a good thing the second reason
I didn't like it there is because it
just doesn't work the way it's supposed
to you probably can't tell this from the
video but the way my car is designed
that position leaves it on an incline
and what I've realized is that the Mochi
doesn't really work if it's not on a
flat surface so later on the video
you'll see I chose to put it on top of
my navigation system not only is it less
distracting I think it looks cooler but
it actually works so let's get into what
this little robot actually does so let
me just start off by saying that it
doesn't do a lot right this is going to
be something that you either fall in
love with or you find extremely boring
and it's just not for you it does react
to your driving so that is something
that's pretty cool when you turn it does
do like a little drift noise and it
changes the image when you suddenly
break and things like that it does do an
animation for that when you accelerate
it has all these different animations
for it it's also constantly playing
these different animations at random so
it's like it's alive on your dash and
it's you know doing faces it it has a
lot of references to different animes
also throughout this video you're going
to see that it makes a reference to
gundam at one point it makes a reference
to Demon Slayer so it has a lot of these
little different random animations along
with also having not random animations
that react to your actual driving so it
has a little gyro or gyroscope inside of
it and it reacts to the way you're
turning and whatnot now it is my
understanding that it does not have a
microphone my understanding is that it
does not receive voice commands and it
doesn't react to your voice or music or
anything like that but with that said
there have been a couple situations that
I'll show you that maybe were just
coincidence but it did seem to react to
things that me and my wife were doing
there's a point here where it does an
animation where my wife is laughing and
the Mochi also starts laughing and it's
not an animation that I saw it do at any
other
point there's also another point where
I'm just holding it in my hands that I'm
looking at it and it starts blowing me
kisses so I that's probably random
sometimes it just does that but I found
that an interesting coincidence I tried
forcing these animations again and I
wasn't able to so I am more than
inclined to believe it does not have a
microphone it only has the gyroscope it
does react to your driving but it does
not react to other things like sounds
music and whatnot that is my
understanding and assumption I tried to
find this information and I couldn't
okay and what else does that do well
that is pretty much it it basically just
sits on your dash it reacts to your
driving and it does different little
animations sounds and different things
that are cute to look at and are pretty
distracting and might cause you to get
in a car accident but at the very least
if that does in fact happen it's going
to be hard for you to stay mad at your
Mochi cuz it's just so cute if I had to
rate this thing on a scale of 1 to 10
and I was first giving you a personal
rating how it makes my heart feel I
would give it a 10 out of 10 but I'm a
nerd if I was thinking about it
objectively you know for somebody that
isn't like me and I was just grading it
based on quality functionality versus
price I would probably either give it a
six or a seven out of 10 if I'm being
completely honest and I say that with
love I told you my personal rating it's
a 10 out of 10 but it's one of those
things that it's very Niche this is
either something that you're going to
love or you're going to hate and you're
going to find it boring and useless
right so you're going to know right away
if you want one or not in my personal
case my whole car is covered in
different anime decals and things from
gundam and whatnot so in my case I
basically Drive the weeb wagon right but
for the average person maybe they
wouldn't get as much enjoyment out of it
as I do so it's going to be one of those
things that it's either for you all the
way or it's really not much like
everything that the size seems to make
because they don't just make the mjis
they also make LED decals and they do
these little devices where your car
makes noises when you turn it on
[Music]
so for example if you're into having
your car greet you with like an anime
phrase or it be like an anime girl
saying something when you turn it on if
you're into that it's great for you but
for the average person they probably
wouldn't like that right so everything
that the sign makes is very Niche and
it's made for people that really like
anime so how much enjoyment you're going
to get out of this or any of the other
products that they make is really going
to depend on where you fall in the scale
cuz maybe you like some of this stuff
but you don't really want it in your car
type of thing maybe you want to keep
your vehicle professional or something
so it's going to be Case by case for the
average person that's kind of looking
for a little robot or a gadget that does
a lot of different things and can get
you know a lot of different uses out of
it this is definitely not the product
finally what I will say is that if you
do want to get one of these I would get
on it because they are constantly out of
stock pretty much anything that this
company makes seems to become an instant
collectible so keep that in mind even
this little Gundam helmet it pretty much
was sold out like in one day they have
these different drops that they do for
different merchandise it's always sold
out everything that they make is
constantly and always sold out not only
are they a small company but they're
definitely targeting like a niche
collector audience every drop that they
have and every product that they make it
seems that they want it to be like
unique and collectible so they don't
make a lot of it so if you do see
anything on their webs site that you do
like I would buy it as soon as you can
because if you don't a scalper probably
will and you're not going to be able to
get a later you're going to have to
negotiate with somebody on eBay or
something like that scalpers have been
annoying about this most of the drops
that they have are not very expensive
but give it a couple days and the
scalpers will have completely bought
everything and it's going to be sold out
and they probably won't replace it it
doesn't seem like any of the limited
edition drops that they have ever come
back which again was the case with this
Gundam stuff it was sold out very quick
and all of it has been sold out ever
since and now pretty much if you want it
you got to trade or negotiate with
somebody online so keep that in mind if
you see something you like snag it
before a scalper does the other thing to
consider is that even if you like it
like I mentioned before it is very
distracting now one thing I neglected to
say you can actually mute it so if you
don't like the noises or the noises
distract you you can mute it if you get
startled easy you know you're probably
going to want to do that because it does
have like police noises at one point
that it does it does have like the sound
of a siren every time it drifts it might
startle you so those are all things that
consider with all of that said a lot of
functionality or not great quality or
not expensive or cheap I love it right
my personal score it's a 10 out of 10 I
absolutely love mine but that is my
review thanks for watching take
[Music]
care for